//creating an array and passing the number,questions,options and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which country won the ICC Cricket World Cup in 2019?",
        answer:"England",
        options:[
             "India",
             "Sri Lanka",
             "England",
             "New Zealand",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What is the highest score ever achieved in a single inning in test cricket ?",
        answer:"952",
        options:[
             "952",
             "914",
             "891",
             "657",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Who won the first ever FIFA World Cup?",
        answer:"Uruguay",
        options:[
             "Brazil",
             "Franch",
             "Argentina",
             "Uruguay",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Who is the leading run scorer in the history of Test cricket?",
        answer:"Sachin Tendulkar ",
        options:[
             "Sanath Jayasooriya",
             "Sachin Tendulkar ",
             "Mahela Jayawardhana",
             "Kumar Sangakkara",
        ]

    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which country won the 2019 Rugby World Cup?",
        answer:"South Africa",
        options:[
             "South Africa",
             "England",
             "New Zealand",
             "Japan",
        ] 
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Who is the current men's singles badminton world champion?",
        answer:"Anders Antonsen",
        options:[
             "Copenhagen",
             "Chen Long",
             "Glasgow ",
             "Anders Antonsen",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Who is the current world champion in men's 100 meters freestyle swimming?",
        answer:"Caeleb Dressel",
        options:[
             "Michael Phelps",
             "Caeleb Dressel",
             "Matt Biondi",
             "Mark Spitz",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Which cricket team has won the most number of ODI World Cups?",
        answer:"Australia",
        options:[
             "Australia",
             "India",
             "Sri Lanka",
             "England",

        ]
    },
    {
        numb:9,
        question: "Which country won the first-ever Rugby World Cup in 1987?",
        answer:"New Zealand",
        options:[
             "New Zealand",
             "Japan",
             "America",
             "korea",
        ]

    },
       
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Who is the most successful female badminton player of all time?",
        answer:"Zhang Ning",
        options:[
             "Nozomi Okuhara",
             "Carolina Mar√≠n",
             "Akane Yamaguchi",
             "Zhang Ning",          
        ]

    },



];